did I understand correctly yes you were collecting drones and
я правильно понял да ты собирал дроны и
ammunition to kill Ukrainians and it
боеприпасы чтобы убивать украинцев а его
blew up in your hand and your face was crooked
разорвало у тебя в руке и лицо покосило
Yes bye yes yes yes Well that is to say it wasn't on the
Да пока Дада Да Ну то есть это не на
front line it was at our house there
передке было это была на хате у нас там
Hello where are you from where am I from Russia
Здравствуйте Вы откуда откуда я с России
And where are you from I am from the city of Khmelnitsky
А вы откуда я из города Хмельницкой
Ukraine What do you think why Russia attacked
Украины Как считаете зачем Россия напала
Ukraine
на Украину
honestly I'll tell you I myself as a
честно вот я вам скажу я вот сам как
contract soldier I just fight purely
контрактник я просто воюю чисто вот
for self-defense of my countries Well
просто для самозащиты вот своих стран Ну
also take the same thing and here from
тоже вот то же самое взять и вот с
Ukraine Like as if I don't get involved in this at the
Украины Типа как бы я в это не лезу в
time Wait you are on a contract and as I
пору Подожди ты на контракте вышь и я
understand it you were cut up by shrapnel You were cut up
так понял это осколками тебя посекло
yes yes Well the drop
Тебя посекло да Да Ну сброс
like from a drone yes from a drone yes yes And where else was he
типа с дрона да с дрона да да А где ещё
wounded and where else was he wounded
ранен а где ещё ранен
in
в
this in the LPR I don't mean except for the face
этом в ЛНР не имею в виду кроме лица
The eye works The eye works the eyes and the hand
Глаз работает Глаз работа глаза и кисть
And what happened to the hand the hand was torn off The hand was torn off the hand
А что с кистью оторвала кисть Кистью
yeah Well I
оторвала кисть ага Ну я в руках его
was sitting in his hands collecting it
сидел собирал
And that is to say you yourself with your drop like
А то есть ты сам своим сбросом типа
burst in
ворвался
yes and that is, you went as a contract soldier
да а то есть ты пошёл контрактником
wanted to make drone drops to kill a
хотел делать дрон сбросы чтобы убить
Ukrainian yes and your arm was torn off and your
украинца да а у тебе оторвало руку и
face was bombed I just do this yes
разбомбило лицо Этим занимаюсь просто да
I have been doing this for 7 years Wait did I
я этим занимаюсь 7 лет Подожди я
understand correctly yes you were collecting drones and
правильно понял да ты собирал дроны и
ammunition to kill Ukrainians and it was torn apart
боеприпасы чтобы убивать украинцев а его
in your hand and your
разорвало у тебя в руке и лицо покосило
face was crooked Yes your face was crooked Yes yes yes yes Well that is, it was
Да лицо покосило Да да да да Ну то есть
not on the front lines it was at
это не на передке было это было на хате
our place there Cool And there were many more like you at that
у нас там Прикольно А много ещё на этой
place
хате было таких как ты
no
нет
two Got it Dob Uh-huh Dob Uh-huh These are the
двое Понял Доб Угу Добр Угу Это вот
kind of things Got it And what happened to
такие вот дела Понял И что случилось у
you what happened well what happened I
тебя что случилось
came to St. Petersburg getting treatment I am enjoying it
ну что в Питер приехал лечусь кайфую
How much was paid out how much was paid out so far
Сколько выплатили сколько выплатили пока
nothing but they should give 3 million for the injury
ещё нисколько но должны 3 млн за ранение
Well everyone is getting it now whether in Ukraine
дать Ну всем сейчас дают что на Украине
or in Russia it makes no difference Everyone is getting 3
что на России без разницы Всем дают по 3
million for the injury It doesn't matter what kind of [ __ ] there is even if there is
млн за ранение Неважно какое там хоть г
no eye there even if there is no hand
хоть глаза не будет там хоть руки не
there everyone is getting it because there is an
будет там всем дают потому что как бы
injury but there is an injury So that's how it
ранение но есть ранение Так то
turns out look that is what  you uh are
получается смотри то есть выходит что ты
going now to get injured like they are
ээ идёшь сейчас на ранение типа тебя
treating you and then you will go to fight again To fight again
лечат а потом пойдёшь снова воевать
yes They are sending me back
Снова воевать да Меня отправляют обратно
Show how they send you if you don't have a
Показывать как отправляют если у тебя
hand If you don't have a hand Well that's how I should
кисти нет Если у тебя кисти нет Ну вот
put the
так вот мне мне ставить категорию
[ __ ] category back That is, they don't put the dka
Гою обратно То есть они дка категорию не
category now Now they don't put the dka category anywhere
ставят сейчас Сейчас нигде д какатегории
Now you have to quit there
не ставят Сейчас что уволится там надо
like because as far as I know for dismissal it's
как потому что за увольнение насколько я
24 million amino defense in Ukraine or
знаю 24 млн аминоборона что на Украине
in Russia they
там что на что в России они сейчас
don't throw money around much now that's why they
деньгами не сильно раскидываются поэтому
don't fire anyone now basically
сейчас никого не увольняют в основном
Now they mostly put the category
Сейчас в основном ставят вот категорию
guide and that is, did I understand correctly that
гайд и то есть я я правильно понял что
your hand was torn off your arm your face was cut and
тебя оторвала кисть с руки секло лицо и
you are still sent to the front
тебя всё равно отправляет на фронт
sent to the front yes That's brutal That's some kind of mockery
отправляет на фронт да Так это жесть Это
Some kind of mockery Now it's like this everywhere Now it's like this everywhere
какое-то Сейчас сейчас везде так Сейчас
And where are you from where are
везде так А ты сам родом откуда откуда
you from Russia Well where are you from Where are you from from
сам с России Ну откуда родом Откуда
Krasnodar Krai
родом с Краснодарского края
Krasnodar Krai When did you go to fight wow
Краснодарский края Когда пошёл воевать
3 months ago So you  I said you've been doing this for 7 years
3 месяца назад Так ты же говорил 7 лет
You've been doing this well 7 years I mean I've been doing
я имею в виду занимаюсь как разтаки вот
this soldering Namely, I went to the front
этим паянием А именно на передок я пошёл
3 months ago
3 месяца назад
That is, you went And where were you
То есть ты пошёл А паянием где ты
doing soldering, there was no war for 7 years Not
занимался это же не было войны 7 лет Не
7 years
7 лет
Again Well, there was no war for 7 years with
Ещё раз Ну так 7 лет не было войны
drones What did you eat there, well, it
дронами Что ж ты там поел
just appeared, as if, and decided to do it It
ну просто вот появилось как бы вот решил
just attracted me Hands, hands don't
заняться Завлекло просто Руки руки не в
grow in principle Why not do it, but
принципе растут Почему бы не заняться да
hands don't grow yes I see that in you The
руки не растут да это я вижу у тебя
main thing is that they grow and the main thing is that they don't Yes Well,
Главное что растут и главное что не Да
as if I lost one hand, like, I don't know Well,
Ну как бы одну кисть потерял типа как бы
nothing terrible, like, I do
не знаю Ну ничего страшного типа я в
n't see the main thing in this I see and everything is great
этом не вижу Главное вижу и всё шикарно
Now I hope it will finally
Сейчас надеюсь она скоро наконец-таки
end soon and everything will be And how old are you I'm
закончится и всё будет А сколько лет
telling you: 18 like how many, how many 18
тебе говорю: 18 типа сколько сколько 18
And so it turns out you were into soldering for 7 years, you got
А то есть ты получается 7 лет увлекался
bang 18, you went and
паянием тебе бахнуло 18 ты пошёл
signed a contract and 3 months and
подписал контракт и 3 месяца и бахнуло
you got bang And you got bang Well, you
тебя И бахнуло тебя
signed an extension Well, you
Ну сосрочки подписал Ну приключения
found yourself an adventure Okay, I'll attract a monus yes
нашёл себе Да Ладно я монус привлечу да
but  with all this you still want to go
но при этом всём хочешь всё равно пойти
to war again Go to war again Well,
снова на войну Ити снова на войну Ну как
like I do
типа я особого прямо такого у меня
n't have any particular desire right now to go back to the
желания сейчас нету возвращаться на
front They just told me that I'm
передок Мне просто сказали то что типа я
supposed to go back because I'm
как бы обязан типа вернуться так как я
recommended there on the front line,
порекомендирован там у них на передке
so Well, and there I don't know, parents are
поэтому Ну а там не знаю родители
lawyers, but you can't send someone to the
адвокаты ну нельзя же отправлять на
front line who's already without an arm Already without an
передок который уже без руки Уже без
arm My mother told me the same thing, that you
руки Матушка мне то же самое говорила то
need a lawyer They don't understand that They
что нужен юрист Они этого не понимают
told me that you'll go
Вот мне сказали то что ты поедешь
back and that's it That is, without any discussion, yes, that they
обратно и всё То есть вот без разговоров
won't hire a lawyer Well, that's
да что юриста не наймут ну это же
mockery An eighteen-year-old
издевательство Восемнадцатилетнего
boy is stupidly driven to his death Death is driven, they've
пацана тупо на смерть гонит Смерть гонит
already hired My mother has already hired her It's all
на наняли уже Уже матушка наняла ей всё
the same to her It's useless at all He says they should have
равно бесполезно вообще Он говорит
fired me, but they put me in
должны были меня уволить но поставили
category G and they keep saying you'll go
вот категорию Г и всё говорят ты поедешь
on vacation, just rest and then
в отпуск просто отдохнёшь и потом
either go back to the base or to the front line That
обратно либо на базу либо на передок То
is, until the war ends, well now,
есть пока война не закончится ну сейчас
as far as I know, until the war
насколько я знаю пока война не
ends, no one will be able to quit
закончится никто не сможет ни уволиться
at all or leave Ukraine at all That is,
вообще ни уйти с Украины вообще То есть
you'll be there until the end That's it
ты будешь находиться там до конца Так
surprise That is, it turns out that the Russians
удиви То есть получается у россиян есть
only have the option of returning through death yes
только вариант через смерть вернуться да
back Well, or until you just straight up
назад Ну либо пока тебя просто прям тебя
neither your legs nor your arms are torn off straight up until the
ни ноги ни руки не оторвёт прямо до
end That is, until you decide Yes, I
конца То есть пока ты не решишься Да я
saw I even saw a video where they
видел я видел видео даже где на костылях
sent men on crutches like back in short back
прислали мужиков типа назад короче назад
Yes, yes, they are also going, going Some are going themselves,
Да да тоже идут идут Некоторые сами идут
some are sent just like that
некоторые некоторых отправляют как раз
What are you where the [ __ ] are you therefore And
таким Что ты где ты [__] поэтому А в
what's the joke, the joke well, I myself don't
чём прикол прикол ну вот я сам этого не
know this Come on, ask Maybe ask a better question Yes
знаю Давай задавай Может задать вопрос
Yes And it turns out like you have a lot of
Да Да А получается типа у вас много вот
conscripts like you went on a contract
таких срочников как ты пошло на контракт
Went on a contract Well, mostly non-
Пошло на контракт Ну в основном не
conscripts mostly just volunteers are
срочники в основном просто добровольцы
going Now most of the mobilized are
идут Сейчас больше всего мобилизованных
mostly That's what in Ukraine, what here
в основном Вот что на Украине что здесь
and in Russia Well, in Russia, it seems there has been no
а в России Так в России же вроде
mobilization for 3 years No, there has been for 3
мобилизации нет уже 3 года Нет уже 3
years Partial, there is Now it is
года есть Частичный есть Сейчас до сих
still mobilizing Mobilizing yes Partial, there
пор мобилизирует Мобилизирует да
are yes There are mobilizations there,
Частичные есть да Там мобилизации там по
how many people, 100 to 200,
сколько по человек по 100 по 200
they are taken to the front Well, it's like there are
забирают на передок Ну типа таких прямо
no such large-scale mobilizations, but in general they are going, we have
масштабных нету мобилизации а вообще
seen  that's why she's fast And who do
идут повидали поэтому она быстро А как
you think is to blame for the fact that you're
ты считаешь кто вот виноват в том что ты
wounded and you're still being
раненый и тебя всё равно короче на
sent to death, death, sent
смерть отправляют смерть отправляют
In general, it's my own fault Well, I essentially
Вообще сам я виноват Ну я сам по сути
went myself As if I knew what I was going to That is,
пошёл Как бы я знал на что я иду То есть
like, well, even despite the
как бы типа ну даже вот даже несмотря на
fact that I'm shell-shocked, like I understand, like, well,
то что я контужный как бы я понимаю типа
I was doing this, like, that is, there's
ну я этим занимался типа то есть там
no need to blame someone for this As
обвинять кого-то в этом ну не надо как
if you were doing this, you were sitting
бы ты вот этим занимался ты сидел это
doing this, it exploded in your hands
делал оно у тебя в руках взорвалось
Okay, yes, that's clear And who is to blame for the
Хорошо да это понятно А кто виноват в
fact that you're being sent back to war,
том что тебя отправляют снова на войну
again to war, honestly That's what I don't
снова на войну честно Вот вот это я не
know
знаю
Well, it seems to me that this is already, you know,
Ну мне кажется это это уже вот знаете
even if we speak trivially, it's already well
это даже вот если вот говорить банально
they don't send them, they just
это уже ну они не отправляют они просто
forcibly send them there, yes, in
принудительно отправляют туда да для
order to just fight back and that's it Well, who is to
того чтобы просто вот отвоеваться и всё
blame, who is to blame for this, who is to
Да ну кто виноват кто в этом виноват кто
blame for this, honestly, I don't know I did
в этом виноват честно не знаю В это
n't really get into it that much Like, I kind
прямо так сильно не вбивался Типа я как
of went, well, I went and went Like, I've
бы пошёл ну пошёл и пошёл Типа как бы я
never been interested in who started
никогда не интересовался кто там начал
this war, who will end it, like,
эту войну кто её будет заканчивать типа
Well, the war is going on, like, I And what do you
как бы Ну идёт война идёт типа Я А как
think  who is to blame for this war in this
считаешь кто виноват в этой войне в этой
honestly these eternal sanctions
честно вот эти вот вечные санкции
sanctions these eternal this
санкции вот эти вот вечные вот эта вот
whole this whole thing with money not with money
вся вот эта конитель с деньгами не с
that is like well I don't think
деньгами то есть как бы ну я не считаю
that like only
то что типа виноват только один
Zelensky is to blame there Trump there someone else I
Зеленский там Трамп там ещё кто-то Я
think that Putin is also to blame
считаю то что и Путин тоже виноват
because when like
потому что когда типа
when like they started talking about the fact that like
когда типа начали говорить по поводу
you like take these
того что типа тебе типа забирать вот эти
parts all of Ukraine when you can just
части все Украины когда ты можешь просто
peacefully allow all this leave something and
мирно это всё разрешить оставить что-то
take something for yourself Well like Putin
и что-то забрать себе Ну как бы Путин
like said that no like this is like
типа сказал то что нет типа это как бы
ours like I'm saying it all started with
наше типа я же говорю вот всё началось
Crimea and it went on I'm
как раз-таки с Крыма и поехало пошло Я
saying I'm not going into details
же говорю я типа в подробности не
like like I'm in a neutral
вливаюсь типа как бы я на нейтральной
country like like I don't care anymore
стране типа как бы мне типа всё равно
That is I understand correctly that
уже То есть я правильно понимаю что
not only Zelensky and Trump are to blame but Putin is also to
виноват не только Зеленский и Трамп но в
blame in something and Putin of
чём-то виноват и Путин да и Путин да
course not only them Not Tra
естественно Конечно не только они Не Тра
A and what is Trump and Zelensky
А а в чём виноват Трамп и Зеленский
Trump and Zelensky to blame damn well well Zelensky
трамп и Зеленский блин вот Ну Зеленский
on the news as far as I watched
по новостям насколько я смотрел
Zelensky is to blame for what he wants  he
Зеленский виноват в том то что он хочет
just doesn't want to make any concessions he
он просто не хочет идти не уступки Он
just wants to end the war
просто то есть хочет завершить войну
Trump now that he has taken the throne he
Трамп сейчас когда он встал на трон он
wants to end the war as soon as possible so that it
хочет войну поскорее закончить чтобы она
not only ends because as
не только закончилась потому что как бы
far as I know Zelensky
насколько я знаю сейчас Зеленский очень
owes the US a lot because the US was
много должен США так как США шла
supplying weapons
поставка оружия
Russia was sort of doing this it was
Россия как бы этим занималась она как бы
sort of doing this itself that is to say the
занималась этим сама То есть типа особо
US wasn't really helping there Now I understood it
там США не помогала Сейчас я так понял
when Trump started negotiating with Putin
когда вот Трамп встал с Путиным на
they, I understood that they
переговоры они так я понял то что они
just want to end this conflict but
просто хотят завершить этот конфликт но
Zelensky isn't letting them do it that is to say
Зеленский не даёт им это сделать То есть
he stands his ground that I
вот вот он стоит на своём то что я типа
will fight to the last until all
буду воевать до последнего пока все
Russian troops sort of leave the
российские войска типа не выйдут с
borders of Ukraine that's why where the photos are there,
границ Украины поэтому там где фотки там
wait it turns out Putin attacked and
так подожди то получается напал Путин а
Zelensky is to blame for not wanting to come to an
виноват Зеленский что не хочет
agreement Did I understand correctly I
договориться Я правильно понял я
understood correctly well in some way that's how it is that is to say
правильно понял ну в каком-то роде это
Trump and
так и есть То есть типа как бы Трамп
Putin are sort of deciding
сейчас с Путиным они как бы решают
now they are trying to somehow resolve it peacefully and
сейчас пытаются мирно как-то решить а
Zelensky isn't really participating in this
Зеленский как бы в этом ну он особо не
when they offered him to
участвует когда ему предлагали как бы
negotiate I mean Trump and
пойти на переговоры В смысле Трамп с
Putin want to end the war and
Путиным хотят типа завершить войну а
Zelensky does not want Zelensky wants
Зеленский не хочет Зеленский хочет
Zelensky says look, it's very simple,
Зеленский говорит смотрите очень просто
Russia withdraws troops from the territory of
Россия забирает войска с территории
Ukraine and that's it, the next day the
Украины и всё на следующий день
war will end The day the war will end
заканчится война День заканчится война
And yes, I heard somewhere they said something like that, they were
И да я слышал где-то говорили такое они
going to exchange prisoners there, something
там собирались меняться пленными там
like that, They were going to
что-то типа Они там пленными собирались
exchange prisoners there, prisoners, civilians there,
меняться пленными там мирными жителями
in short,
короче
Well, I don't know how I would, I'm saying that I do
Ну не знаю как бы я я же говорю я об
n't really know much about it, like, damn, No, that's not
этом особо как бы не шарю типа блин Не
it, what is Zelensky's fault, look,
не так в чём виноват Зеленский смотри
Putin attacked, Zelensky says: "We want to
Путин напал Зеленский говорит: "Мы хотим
stop the war, Just withdraw troops
остановить войну Просто заберите войска
from Ukraine and that's it." And the war stops,
с Украины и всё" И война останавливается
but Putin doesn't want it. So
а Путин не хочет Так в чм виноват
Zelensky is to blame for the World Cup, Zelensky is to blame for the World Cup, all this is
Зеленский в чм виноват Зеленский всё это
elementary. Now Zelensky is simply to
элементарно Сейчас Зеленский просто
blame for me. Now, if we consider from
виноват для меня Вот если вот считать с
my side, he is to blame for the fact that he
моей стороны он виноват в том то что он
simply did not immediately make concessions when
просто сразу не пошёл на уступки когда
Putin offered him to negotiate. We
ему Путин предлагал встать на переговоры
live in the world, what concessions should he have made,
Мире живём на какие уступки он должен
wait, Putin attacks
был пойти подожди Путин нападает на
Ukraine, yes, in order to seize it or
Украину да чтобы её захватить её либо
part of it, he says, in order to give up part of Ukraine.
часть говорит чтобы отдать часть Украины
Zelensky says: "Yes, you are like saying you are to
Зеленский говорит: "Да ты типа говоришь
blame  Zelensky" Like
виноват Зеленский" Типа виноват
Zelensky is to blame Everything broke off That's how It was a
Зеленский Всё оборвался Вот так Это была
bomb-rocket What a character we have
бомба-ракета Вот это у нас персонаж
[laughter]
[смех]
Yes, 18 years old, went from conscription to a contract
да 18 лет со срочки пошёл на контракт
He wanted to have Ukrainians there and
Захотелось ему там украинцев да
pip-pip-pip yes And there he was afraid of something and
почик-чик-чикать да А там что-то боял и
bang and that's
бабах и
it Because golden hands and will not
всё Потому что золотые руки и не
grow If you want more of these
израстут Если хотите чтобы больше было
golden boys who have
золотых таких мальчиков да у которых
hands that
руки
do not grow, subscribe to the channel, put a
нерастут подпишитесь на канал поставьте
like, leave a comment yes for how much you
лайк коммент оставьте да на сколько вы
want and send this video to your friends
этого хотите и скиньте это видео друзьям
Bingo Subscribe to Telegram right
Бинго Підпишись на й Telegram прямо
now Os in And
зараз Ось вн А
priest this is very and very important YouTube
попик це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube
drives us through the card into a shadow ban
заганяє нас через каргеор в тіньовий бан
and very many videos are not shown to people
и дуже багато відео не показуется людям
at times does not show information about streams
вчасно не показуец інформація про стрими
so that we have a small operational connection
для того щоб ми мали оперативный зв'язок
subscribe right now a  priest there in
підпишиться прямо зараз а попик там в
telegram okmdeo also interesting and useful
телеграмі окмдео ще теж цікава и корисна
information and we are obliged to receive constant
інформація и мы повин трима постійний
operational communication
оперативний зв'язок
Independently from that ci will show you about it
Незалежно від того чи покаже вам про цей
YouTube Glory to Ukraine subscribe
YouTube Слава Україні підпишись